let's get right into it huh the comedy's
going good it's going good I just signed
up to drive for Lift
um God doesn't make mistakes but I got a
couple family members last time I was
hit on a white Co she was like hey you
want to go back to my place I go back to
her place she had me fix the computer
while she passed out on the couch so I'm
in Target to get myself ready she's
crying so hard I go right up to her and
I'm like excuse me ma'am uh I think you
mean to be in Walmart right now so
I think the stupidest thing the cops do
is they'll set up a du checkpoint I get
so nervous you know it's like I'm stone
cold sober but I'm like it's police like
luring the back windows they're like
lure the front windows like you know
what let's just go to jail
okay oh Smiley how come you're not
smiling you got a last name Smiley you
ought to smile all the time we're going
to call you Mr frownie Mr Smiley and as
the good book says do not go to sleep on
your anger which means a man cannot
sleep until he dies